Batwo AI Marketing - ads_read Permission Demo
This permission allows users to read campaign performance data.
Navigate to the Dashboard main page.
KPI (Key Performance Indicator) cards are displayed at the top.
First card: ROAS (Return on Ad Spend)
ROAS: 3.45 (₩3.45 revenue per ₩1 spent)
API call: GET /act_/insights?fields=roas
Second card: Total Spend
Total Spend: ₩1,234,567
API call: GET /act_/insights?fields=spend
Third card: Conversions
Conversions: 358
API call: GET /act_/insights?fields=conversions
Fourth card: CTR (Click-Through Rate)
CTR: 2.34%
API call: GET /act_/insights?fields=ctr
Scroll down to see the performance charts.
First chart: Daily Spend Trend
Last 7 days of spending data shown as a bar chart.
API call: GET /act_/insights?time_range=
Second chart: ROAS Trend
Daily ROAS changes shown as a line graph.
Highest ROAS is 4.12, lowest is 2.89.
Continue scrolling to see the campaign performance table.
Campaign list table is displayed.
Performance metrics for each campaign are shown:
- Campaign Name
- Spend
- Impressions
- Clicks
- ROAS
"Summer Campaign 2024": ₩500,000 spend, ROAS 3.67
"Flash Sale Week": ₩300,000 spend, ROAS 2.89
"New Product Launch": ₩434,567 spend, ROAS 3.55
API call: GET /act_/campaigns?fields=name,spend,insights
Click on a campaign to view detailed information.
Campaign detail page is displayed.
Campaign name: "Summer Campaign 2024"
Detailed performance metrics:
- Impressions: 145,678
- Clicks: 3,421
- Spend: ₩500,000
- Conversions: 156
- CPC: ₩146
- Conversion Rate: 4.56%
API call: GET /act_/insights with detailed metrics
With ads_read permission, you can:
- View real-time KPI dashboard
- Check campaign performance data
- Analyze daily, weekly, and monthly trends
- Generate performance-based reports
Users always see the latest campaign data.
Dashboard data is synced in real-time from Meta.
ads_read permission demo completed.