Batwo AI Marketing - pages_show_list Permission Demo
This permission allows users to view their managed Facebook Pages.
Click the Settings menu.
Select "Meta Pages Management" from the Settings menu.
The Meta Pages Management page is displayed.
Click the "Connect Meta Account" button.
Facebook login dialog is displayed.
Enter test email.
Enter password.
Click the "Log In" button.
Permission consent screen is displayed.
Requested Permissions:
- pages_show_list
- pages_read_engagement
- business_management
- ads_read
- ads_management
Click the "Continue" button.
Facebook authentication is completed.
API call: GET /me/accounts (using pages_show_list permission)
User's Facebook Pages list is loaded.
Pages list displayed:
Page 1: "My Fashion Store"
- Category: Online Retail
- Followers: 15,234
- Status: Active
Page 2: "Beauty Products"
- Category: Beauty/Cosmetics
- Followers: 8,567
- Status: Active
Page 3: "Home & Living"
- Category: Home Decor
- Followers: 12,890
- Status: Active
Each page includes the following information:
- Page Name
- Page Category
- Total Followers
- Page Status (Active/Inactive)
Click the first page "My Fashion Store".
Page detail information page is displayed.
Page Name: "My Fashion Store"
Page ID: 1234567890
Category: Online Retail
Total Followers: 15,234
Page Description: "Your go-to fashion destination"
Page Created: March 15, 2022
Page Link: https://facebook.com/myfashionstore
Click "View Analytics" to check engagement data.
(This uses pages_read_engagement permission)
Click Pages List button to return.
Other pages can be viewed the same way.
Select the "Beauty Products" page as well.
Page: "Beauty Products"
- Followers: 8,567
- Category: Beauty/Cosmetics
With pages_show_list permission, you can:
- View all Facebook Pages managed by the user
- Check basic page information (name, category, followers)
- Select pages to use other features
Users can manage multiple pages at once.
Analytics and advertising are managed separately for each page.
pages_show_list permission demo completed.