Batwo AI Marketing - pages_read_engagement Permission Demo
This permission allows users to read engagement data from Facebook Pages.
Select "Meta Pages Management" from the Settings menu.
List of connected pages is displayed.
Click the "My Fashion Store" page.
Page detail page is displayed.
Click the "View Analytics" tab.
API call: GET //insights (using pages_read_engagement permission)
Page engagement analytics dashboard is displayed.
Key metrics in the dashboard:
1. Fans (Total Followers)
- Fan Count: 15,234
2. Page Impressions (28-day period)
- Impressions: 125,678
3. Engaged Users
- Engaged Users: 8,934
4. Post Engagement
- Total Engagement: 23,456 (likes/comments/shares)
API call: GET //insights?metric=page_fans
API call: GET //insights?metric=page_impressions
API call: GET //insights?metric=page_engaged_users
Scroll to recent posts section.
Engagement data for recent Facebook posts is displayed.
Post 1 (January 23, 2024)
Title: "Winter Collection Launch - New Arrivals"
Engagement Metrics:
- Likes: 342
- Comments: 67
- Shares: 23
Engagement Rate: 5.23%
Post 2 (January 21, 2024)
Title: "Flash Sale - 50% Off Selected Items"
Engagement Metrics:
- Likes: 1,245
- Comments: 234
- Shares: 156
Engagement Rate: 8.67%
Post 3 (January 19, 2024)
Title: "Customer Testimonial - Happy Customer Feature"
Engagement Metrics:
- Likes: 567
- Comments: 89
- Shares: 34
Engagement Rate: 6.12%
API call: GET //posts?fields=story,shares.limit(0).summary(true)
Period-based engagement trend chart is displayed.
Daily engagement trend for the last 7 days:
Jan 17: 2,345 engagements
Jan 18: 3,123 engagements (Flash Sale)
Jan 19: 3,890 engagements
Jan 20: 2,567 engagements
Jan 21: 4,234 engagements (Flash Sale)
Jan 22: 2,145 engagements
Jan 23: 1,876 engagements
Daily changes are visualized in a line chart.
Ratio of likes vs comments vs shares is displayed.
Likes: 71%
Comments: 18%
Shares: 11%
Peak engagement hours are displayed.
Peak engagement hours: 2-4 PM (14:00-16:00)
Second peak: 7-9 PM (19:00-21:00)
Fan growth trend is displayed.
Fan Growth (last 30 days):
15,000 (30 days ago) → 15,234 (today)
Net Growth: +234 fans
With pages_read_engagement permission, you can:
- View fan count and growth trends
- Check page impressions and reach
- View post-level engagement data (likes, comments, shares)
- Analyze engagement trends over time
- Identify peak engagement hours
- Discover high-engagement content
E-commerce merchants can use this data to plan marketing strategy.
Decide when and what content to post.
pages_read_engagement permission demo completed.