Batwo AI Marketing Solution
Meta App Review Demo
This video demonstrates the end-to-end experience
for each requested Meta permission.
The app is loaded at the Campaigns page.
Real campaign data from Meta Ads is displayed.
Multiple campaigns are shown with status,
budget, and ROAS metrics.
This demonstrates that the app is connected
to Meta and has real data access.
Navigating to the App Review Demo page
to show all requested permissions.
Meta Account Connection Status: Connected
All 5 requested permissions are displayed:
1. pages_show_list - GRANTED
Display list of Facebook Pages managed by the user
2. pages_read_engagement - GRANTED
Read engagement metrics from Pages
3. business_management - GRANTED
Manage business assets including Meta Pixels
4. ads_read - GRANTED
Read campaign performance data and insights
5. ads_management - GRANTED
Create, update, and manage advertising campaigns
Feature Demonstrations section shows
all permission use cases.
API Endpoints table shows the
Meta Graph API calls used by this application.
Now demonstrating pages_show_list permission.
Navigating to Settings > Meta Pages Management
API Call: GET /me/accounts
This retrieves the list of Facebook Pages.
The user's Facebook Page is displayed:
"BATWO Company" page
Page details include name, category,
and follower count.
pages_show_list permission allows users
to select which Page to use with our app.
Now demonstrating ads_read permission.
Navigating to the Dashboard page.
KPI cards are displayed at the top:
ROAS, Total Spend, Conversions, CTR
API Call: GET /act_/insights
Real-time performance data from Meta.
The dashboard shows campaign performance
fetched directly from Meta Ads API.
AI Insights section provides automated
recommendations based on campaign data.
Active campaigns table shows all
campaigns with their performance metrics.
Scrolling to see more dashboard content
and campaign analytics.
Now demonstrating ads_management permission.
Navigating to the Campaigns page.
Campaign list shows existing campaigns
with status indicators.
Each campaign displays: name, objective,
daily budget, spend, and ROAS.
Action buttons allow users to Edit
or view Analytics for each campaign.
Multiple campaigns visible: LEADS campaigns,
Traffic campaigns with various budgets.
Scrolling to show more campaigns
in the list.
Now navigating to Create New Campaign page.
Campaign creation form with quick-start templates.
Available templates:
- Traffic: Drive website visitors
- Conversions: Maximize purchases
- Brand Awareness: Reach new audiences
- Engagement: Increase interactions
- Lead Collection: Gather customer info
Each template pre-configures objective,
budget, and targeting settings.
API Call: POST /act_/campaigns
Creates campaign in Meta Ads Manager.
Users can also set up campaigns manually
without using templates.
Now demonstrating business_management permission.
Navigating to Settings page.
Settings menu shows:
- Meta Ad Account connection
- Pixel Installation
Pixel Installation uses business_management
to manage Meta Pixels.
API Calls: GET /me/businesses
GET //adspixels
Users can view, select, and manage
their Meta Pixels for conversion tracking.
Returning to App Review Demo page
for final summary.
All 5 permissions have been demonstrated:
pages_show_list - View Facebook Pages
pages_read_engagement - Read Page metrics
business_management - Manage Pixels
ads_read - View campaign performance
ads_management - Create and manage campaigns
All permissions are GRANTED and
actively used by this application.
Batwo AI Marketing Solution provides
e-commerce advertising automation.
Users can manage all their Meta advertising
through a single integrated platform.
Thank you for reviewing our application.
For questions, contact: support@batwo.ai
Batwo AI Marketing Solution
Meta App Review Demo - Complete